I'll look for Shangguan Eagle.
Your task now
is to rest well.
If you act on your own again,
I'll discipline you.
What are you looking at?
What are you thinking?
This is the first time
to see you so sharp.
has completely changed my memory.
It's quite scary.
You're still the same.
You can't even pull back what you want.
[But when I met you,]
[I'm Son Goku. I'm wearing the cudgel.]
You're not getting any better.
You're my superior after all.
You couldn't beat me when I was young.
You still can't defeat me when you grow up.
If you have no reason, you have to admit defeat.
Fine.
I admit defeat.
Uncle.
I heard from my brother
my father's death is related to the National Party.
What happened?
I just remembered it later.
The one who conspired with Jennifer Chae
I think I've seen them in Jang Gong-yeon's team.
Some are still officials.
If we let them go down the mountain,
If everyone knows,
they were angry.
I can’t go down the mountain to avenge your father.
Besides,
I told you before your father's spirit
to lead everyone to find the murderer.
Don't say I can't stop him.
I can.
How could I
stop the passion of my brothers?
Uncle
Jang Gong-yeon is stationed there.
If we do it,
we'll die.
Eagle.
We're just going to
on Jang Gong-yeon.
If they did it,
I can make him hand over the murderer as soon as possible.
Jang Gong-yeon.
I'm scared.
Nothing dangerous.
Then we will become bandits
to bandits against the government.
This is not what my father wants.
It's not that everyone doesn't want to be a good person.
but the government has gone too far.
Besides, your father
by someone.
We must take revenge.
I told them
not to go too far.
Don't worry, Eagle.
I know what to do.
Go and rest.
Master.
There are swordsmen outside.
They've surrounded our command centre.
We can't go anywhere.
It's upside down.
The bandits are coming.
This is outrageous!
We were caught off guard
we were caught off guard.
Now we have a continuous force.
We have light machine guns and machine guns.
Let's open the door and shoot them back.
No.
We can't underestimate the enemy.
There are more than 100,000 swordsmen.
We don't know how many he's here.
If we open the door, it's like opening the door and stealing.
and burn ourselves to death.
How about we call
to send someone back?
It’s too late.
These bandits have surrounded us.
Even if we defend all the 16 division,
we can’t get rid of our thirst.
Master,
We can't just sit and do nothing.
Call Cui Wenkui
Ask his independent Brigade to save me.
Independent Brigade has always been against us.
Cui Wenkui is always against you.
Is it appropriate to call him back?
We are all brothers of the army.
I'm in trouble now.
He can't just let me die.
If he doesn't come,
you have to beg him to come.
If he comes, I'll agree to anything.
Call him. Yes.
Yes.
Got it.
Brigade Commander, what's Zhang Gongyan's order?
Zhang Gongyan said his division
was surrounded by swordsmen.
and asked us to send reinforcements.
Zhang Gong Yan is really something.
A commander of the legitimate lineage
has heavy soldiers.
The command centre was taken down twice.
Zhang Gongyun also said
Shangguan Bao died.
What?
Shangguan Bao is dead.
Should we save him or not?
Yes.
How?
Those swordsmen put down their weapons and they are the people.
They're bandits when they pick up their weapons.
How can we save them without distinguishing the enemy?
Brigade Commander.
We can't disobey the order.
If Jang Gong Yeon was killed by the swordsman,
we won't be able to get away with it.
I know what you are talking about.
This time, the Japanese
is actually the Japanese.
They want to frame Shangguan Bao's death on the national army.
They want the army and swordsmen to kill each other.
so that they can take advantage of it.
Japanese?
Luckily we didn't send troops.
Otherwise, the consequences would be unimaginable.
If no one takes care of this,
it will be a fierce battle
it will be a fierce battle.
Although Jang Gong-yeon is unreliable,
but he can still stabilize people in Shaanxi.
So we can't sit back and watch.
So...
you mean
I came to you
because I want you
with me
to clarify the misunderstanding.
No.
They are looking for a chance
to attack us.
At this time,
we have to go to her house.
I think Ms. Cai's idea
is feasible.
Okay.
I'll arrange someone.
No need.
I'll go with her.
Brigade Commander.
Mr. He.
Where's Masao Tahara?
Didn't we agree to meet here?
Mr. He did a great job this time.
Mr. Tian Yuan is preparing
to welcome you.
Please follow me.
Major, he's here.
Mr. He is here.
Have a seat.
I've done
what you asked me to do.
Are we even now?
Mr. He,
We had a great cooperation.
Why did you give up halfway?
You are the most loyal friend
of the Japanese army.
We have many honorable missions
We can do it together.
I've had enough.
I live in nightmares all day.
I can see
when Shangguan Bao died.
I just want to get rid of this as soon as possible.
The only chance you have now
is to help the Japanese army
to take over the city.
There will be Japanese flags here.
Look at them.
when you look at them.
As you ordered,
I instigated the swordsman
and the hatred between the army.
You should fulfill your promise.
He,
From the moment you helped me kill Shangguan Bao,
you have lost
to control your own destiny.
Listen to me.
When you become the head of Qinglong Camp,
and let those swordsmen
to serve us,
I will
you will be free.
Qinglong Fortress belongs to Shangguan Eagle.
Not mine.
I swore in front of everyone.
It's just temporary.
Then let's make it official.
If you can't do it,
your family will pay for it.
Think about this carefully.
Masao Tahara.
You're a despicable villain!
You're going too far. You're a man of your word.
You're not a man!
Are you done?
Go back to work if you're done.
The royal army is going west.
I don't have that much time for you.
Major.
Now He Xiaopian and the swordsman
are under our control.
The army of Shaanxi will collapse at any time.
You did a great job.
As long as no one shot the first shot in Shanzhou,
there's a high chance that something else will happen.
We can't let our guard down.
Let me help them.
The first shot to strike the civil unrest in Shanzhou.
Stop! Stop!
Guys, don’t get me wrong.
We’re here to pay our respects.
We mean no harm.
You killed Madam.
How dare you come up the mountain to worship?
How dare you!
There is indeed a misunderstanding about killing Madam.
We’re here to clarify it.
Please tell us.
It's easy to enter the mountain.
Tie her up and let her deal with it.
Miss Cai, you're quite bold.
This is your temporary plan.
We are tied here alive.
Why do I feel that our lives
our lives today?
You should have thought about it before you came.
I don't think so.
My wish is to die on the battlefield.
Will I
sacrifice with you later?
Miss Leng.
Are you here to worship my father?
You're guests.
Untie him.
But the army killed Madam.
A wrong has a source, a debt has its debtor.
We must take revenge.
But you can't kill the innocent.
Untie me.
You're right.
Miss Leng is righteous and polite.
You really have the style of Patriarch.
It’s a pity that
was killed by a villain.
It's a great loss to the Three Dukedoms.
My condolences, Miss Shangguan.
You two went up the mountain today
to go up the mountain today?
Tell me.
What is it?
Since you said so,
we don't have to beat around the bush.
Actually, we came here today
to clarify something.
Someone said
that our army killed the leader.
and caused a misunderstanding between the swordsmen and the army.
The chaos in Shanzhou is triggered.
But now the war is coming.
If we kill each other,
the Japanese will have a chance.
By then,
to occupy the whole city.
I believe these are not what we want to see.
Miss Cai is right.
This is just a fear.
If the Japanese
between the Japanese,
it will be very troublesome.
Of course, if we know
who the murderer is,
if we catch him,
we will send him to Qinglong Fortress as soon as possible
and give him to Miss Shangguan.
My father
never hurt the people
because of personal grudges.
I won't do anything
and do things that make your family happy.
I can promise you
to let the swordsman leave Shanzhou temporarily.
But if I know
someone in your army
related to my father's death?
I will make sure you give me an explanation.
We thank you
for the soldiers in Shaanxi.
Is something bothering you?
Say something else.
My sister always asked me
Brother, is something bothering you?
Just like a worm in my stomach.
No.
I was thinking
Shangguan Eagle let us go so easily.
Is it that simple?
I didn't expect it to go so smoothly.
But isn't this what we want?
We promised her
to help her find the murderer.
Where can we find her?
One more thing.
It has something to do with Jennifer Cai.
You said it has something to do with vegetable buns?
Someone said Cai Yun killed Shangguan Bao.
Don’t you believe me?
Wait.
In other words,
Shangguan Eagle is looking for vegetable buns.
If we help Shangguan eagle find the vegetable buns
and send them to Qinglong Camp,
it has nothing to do
with our army.
You have to hand Cai Yun over to Shangguan Eagle.
I think our priority now
is to find the steamed buns.
We're done talking.
Let's talk about private matters.
What personal matter?
Did you save Cai?
Yes.
Where is he?
He's recuperating.
After meeting you at Qinglong Fortress,
the wound cracked again.
I won't disobey my father.
But I can’t
for killing my father.
Give him to me.
Do you really believe Cai Yun killed your father?
If you really believe it,
you wouldn't have come to me now.
If you didn't come to me,
I would have gone to you.
Think about
What kind of person is she?
He came to Luoyang City
to Luoyang City full of Japanese soldiers to steal medicine.
The last chance to escape
to Huo Lang and me.
but he almost sacrificed himself.
A man of justice and faith
would never kill
who treated him like his son?
I know everything you said.
How do you explain it?
Someone saw Cai Yun's murder.
Someone saw Cai killed your father.
Who?
Mr. He.
Mr. He saw Cai killed my father with his own eyes.
Master He saw
Cai Yun killed your father.
Yes.
Master He is the witness.
Among your father's accomplices, there's a national army.
Yes.
What do you mean?
You think Mr. He is lying?
Impossible.
Mr. He was the person my father trusted the most.
He has no reason to lie.
I can guarantee with my life.
Cai will never kill your father.
But Master He said he saw it.
There must be something wrong.
[Eagle, you're here.] [I'm here.]
Why are you here?
I was waiting for you.
Wait for me?
What is it?
Cai Jin and Cui Wenkui are here.
to pay tribute to my father.
They came to pay tribute to your father.
My brothers detained them.
I stopped them.
They came to make peace.
I think they have a point.
At this time,
we shouldn't fight with the army anymore.
What about your father?
They are so lucky.
Didn't you say
we can’t confirm the people of the army
is related to my father's death.
For something uncertain,
for something uncertain.
It's not appropriate.
But if my father were alive,
he would want us
to leave Shanzhou for now.
I hope you can support me.
Okay.
Although this is our revenge,
in the end,
your family hatred.
Since you can let it go,
what else can I say?
Uncle.
One more thing.
to ask you.
Go ahead.
You always said that
killed my father
he killed my father.
But my father has agreed to our marriage.
If he marries me,
Qinglong Fortress will belong to him sooner or later.
Why did he do that?
Yeah.
I can't figure this out either.
The hardest thing in the world is human heart.
We only know
who we've only known
How much do you know about her?
But Uncle, Eagle,
I'm tired.
Let's talk tomorrow.
Are you rebelling?
Surround the command centre.
Disrupting military commander.
This is a capital crime.
Fortunately, Division Commander Zhang is kind.
and let it go.
Get out of here!
Listen.
As long as you hand over the murderer,
we’ll leave right away.
Our command centre
No one went out last month.
Even if there is,
you should give us time to investigate.
Mr. Taniwara is really clever.
It seems that even if we don't shoot,
they will fight.
I believe we can go back to report soon.
You just want to buy time
so that the murderer can escape.
We won't fall for your trap.
You can't find it.
Let us go in and find it ourselves.
Tie them up one by one and let him recognize them.
Ridiculous!
Guards!
If anyone comes any closer,
Kill him!
Guys, go!
Stop!
Brigade Commander Cui, you're finally here.
Young Lady Zhen Zhu.
These scoundrels.
Put the gun down first.
Help us arrest them.
Brigade Commander Cui, where are your men?
Let me tell you.
I asked Ms. Shangguan
is more useful than my entire Brigade.
Put the gun down.
Guys.
I know you came down the mountain for Qinglong Fortress.
for my father.
I will never forget your kindness.
But we don't have solid evidence yet.
that the 16th Division is related to my father's death.
We can't act rashly.
The most important Japanese army
is over a dozen miles away.
War will break out anytime.
Once a war breaks out,
the whole city will suffer.
How should we face this disaster?
I believe my father
in the underworld.
Young Lady.
Should we just let them go?
We're just leaving temporarily.
Once this war is over,
if the 16th Division
really related to my father's death,
they will pay with their blood.
Yes, blood for blood!
Blood for blood!
Oh no!
This woman is going to ruin our plan.
Let's go.
Guys, let's go.
Who shot? Is it your army?
Go!
I'll kill you! Calm down!
Calm down! Don't shoot! Put the gun down!
Are you okay?
It wasn't our people.
If it was,
he wouldn't have shot now.
It must be the Japanese who sowed discord.
Guys, listen to me.
Let's go.
Miss Leng, let's go.
Guys, let’s go.
Take Miss Shangguan to the hospital.
Stop.
Why are you here?
I'm here to see someone.
Do you know everyone is looking for you?
Are you looking for Shangguan Eagle?
Aren't you afraid that she'll shoot you again?
She won't kill me with one shot.
I will still come to see her.
It's been a while.
Now you're a romantic.
Okay.
Let me give you a ride.
No need.
I can walk.
Look at your face.
I'm afraid you can't go there.
and died on the road.
I have to go with her for emergency treatment.
Emergency?
Is she hurt badly?
I'm worried.
Go check it out yourself.
Fine, I won't stand on ceremony with you.
Let's go.
Take care.
Cui Wenkui.
Why did you bring me here
to bring me here?
Bao.
You killed Shangguan Bao.
has dragged our army
into the water.
I can't explain myself.
Please explain to them yourself.
Do you also believe that I will kill Shangguan Bao?
I don't care
who killed Shangguan Bao.
But now,
the anti-Japanese situation in Shanzhou
has been destroyed.
Why are you laughing?
I just remembered the past.
I witnessed your father capture my father.
Now you've arrested me.
You inherit your father's business.
If you do that,
my father was killed by the Communist Party.
Why do you keep picking on me?
You can't tell right from wrong.
It turns out that you have a grudge here.
Fine.
Take things as they come.
The person who told you
Prepare me a single room and something delicious.
If anything happens to me,
you'll be in big trouble.
Lead the way.
Guards!
Take him in.
How is it?
Any news from Jennifer Chae?
He was locked up
in a military prison of independent brigade.
Cui Wenkui plans to
tomorrow morning.
If he goes to Qinglong Hideout,
he will die in vain.
Can we organise a rescue
rob a car
or break into the prison.
We can't break into the prison.
The prison is heavily guarded.
With our current weapons,
if we attack hard,
not only did he fail, but also suffered heavy casualties.
I can't just watch him die.
He knows he owes Shangguan Eagle.
to make up for it.
Now that I know she's in danger,
she will lose control of her emotions.
He saved my life
in Luoyang City.
He's a loyal man.
I can't watch him
see him die.
I will save him
to save him.
Don't worry.
There's a way.
What can I do?
Miss Cai.
Why don't you come to San Bao Hall?
What? Who do you want to save with me this time?
Or do you have any other request?
I want you to release Cai.
What did you say?
You told me to put some vegetables in it.
Who are you to say that to me?
Beg me.
I have the right to refuse.
What if you order me?
We are in different units now.
I think I can't help you
I can't help you.
Cai once helped us in Shanzhou.
and saved the army.
Now we arrest him.
Aren't you afraid that people will talk about us?
being ungrateful?
I know what you said.
what you said.
But...
don't forget a fact.
He has a life on his back.
We have witness and evidence.
The law can't be more generous.
Unless...
Unless you have the command from the First Warfare Command.
Otherwise,
I can't help you.
What if I ask you as your sister?
Brother.
You finally acknowledge me, right?
Now,
finally acknowledge me.
Do you know
when I first saw you,
I was sure you were Wen Pei.
A, lion, 30, army.
Travel 72.
As a reporter,
as a military commander,
appeared beside me,
I didn't dare to ask.
I'm afraid you'll be in danger.
I know you have a mission.
Do you know why I sent someone
to follow you 24 hours a day?
Why did I save Shangguan eagle
I went to save her.
For the sake of public interest.
Yes, I know.
I have a mission.
so I had to hide it from you.
I'm sorry.
You've grown up.
I don't even dare to recognize you.
We can meet again today.
We should thank our father for his blessing.
Ni, where are you going?
I'm looking for my mother.
My mother hasn't come back yet.
Uncle Liu, did you see her?
I didn't notice.
I'll look for it.
She's always in a hurry.
Brother.
I know your father's death is a big blow to you.
But it has nothing to do with Bao.
It has nothing to do with him.
Do you know what he is now?
He's a Communist Party.
We are the Republican Party.
We're in different levels.
And don't forget one thing.
Our biological father was killed by the Communist Party.
The Communist Party had blood on his hands.
We were young when my father died.
What does it have to do with him?
Besides, his father is dead.
I don't care.
But he's a commie, right?
I've been suspecting that
my father's death wasn't that simple.
Before I find out the truth,
I hope you won't target him.
The three of us grew up together.
For me,
are also our family.
Bao is your family.
Who am I?
Am I your family?
He's your family. Is he looking for you?
I've been looking for you for so many years.
Don't tell me you like him.
No.
That's good.
Forget it.
I was wrong.
I can't watch you cry.
I'm happy today.
I'll ask them to prepare some dishes.
Let's have a good chat.
What have you been doing these years?
Brother.
No matter what,
I'll take the buns with me.
Sorry.
Come in.
I suspect
Brigade Commander Cui is suspected of colluding.
Take him away for investigation.
Also, my informant Chae was arrested by him.
Release him now.
Drop your guns and get out.
Get out!
Where did he go?
You're making a big joke.
A real sister who has been waiting for her return.
pointed a gun at him
and put him in jail.
Cui Wenkui
must hate me so much.
I had no choice.
In order to save you,
in order to save you.
How are you going to thank her?
What else can I do?
I'll take a few more bullets for her.
By the way,
What are you going to do next?
I can't keep him locked up.
Actor table.
Zhang Wen.
and actors.
Su Tianhui, Yang Wanlin, Zhao Dongliang, Chen Yile, Wang Lusheng.
Li Shuo Yu Hongda Tian Guofeng Gong Fan Cheng Kaiyan
Sun Zhaoqi, Li Sheng, Yang Haoyu, Zhou Chaoyang.
to perform.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao, Sun Haochun.
Qin Haosen, Liu Mingjun, Zhang, Liang, Lin, Nan.
Liu Fei, Du Geng, Yuan Zhiwei.
The staff table.
Director team.
Zhu Shaojie.
The production team.
Photography team.
Sun Yongqing.
Ding Weihao.
Lighting Team.
Costume team.
The dressing team.
Art team.
Zeng So-wook.
Zhang Zefeng.
Props team.
Wu Weiguo.
Cui Guangzang.
Set team.
Action team.
Fireworks.
The gun team.
The recording team.
The venue team.
Driver team.
Su Gao Feng, Liu Deyu, Zhai Yongming, Zou Youwei.
Chen Jianqi Zhang Kun Wu Gold Baby Zhang Rong Li Zhang Chang
Teng Tie Yan, Xu Ian, Zhang Choo Qiang, Yang Yijiang.
Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang, Zhang Jianping.
Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang, Zhang Jianping
Yang Shuli, Chen Yongsheng, Liu Junfeng, Liu Fu Min
behind the scenes, Shin Bae-jin.
[Late production]
ZMCG.
Beijing Zhuma Chenguang Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing JUMAJUANG MEDIA Co., Ltd.
Late production.
Wang Chenyang.
dubber
Music production.
Theme song, Hero.
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for the title of this drama.
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for the name of the film.
Thank you.
Shandong Blumund Red Film Club. [National 4A Scene Area]
Henan Juntong Car Co., Ltd.
Henan Juntong Co., Ltd.
The Public Government of Shanzhou District
The People's Government of Xizhang Village, Shanzhou District
The temple in the village in Shanzhou District.
[Dandelion Theatre, San Mun.]
The temple in Shanzhou District
[Seobu Village Committee of Lingbao City]
The village committee of Shanzhou District,
Jiangzhou Zhou Jiajun Co., Ltd.
legal consultant service unit.
Henan Lu Da Law Firm.
Special cooperation unit.
There are three Municipal Committee in total.
The People's Government
The PR Department of the Municipal Committee
The Commission of Shanzhou
The Commissioner of Wonji County
The People's Government of Shanzhou District.
The People's Government of Wenji County.
Henan Henan Boutique Co., Ltd.
The Cultural Responsibility Co., Ltd.
[Tianan Lake City humidy park, San Mumei.]
Gate Hua Cultural Tourism Investment Group.
Sanmen Cultural Tourism Investment Group.
Yang Tingxuan.
The guidance unit.
Learning to strengthen our country.
The circulation unit.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Control unit.
Henan Sandao Movie Development Co., Ltd.
[Joint Film Co., Ltd.]
[Joint filming unit]
The PR Department of Gansu Provincial Committee
Henan Provincial Radio Station.
Henan Provincial Literature and Arts Association.
Henan Provincial Film Association.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Gansu Lanyi Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing Times, Yishi Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Hebei Army Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Product unit.
[Henan Movie Development Co., Ltd.]
Henan Elephant Film and TV Production Co., Ltd.
Zhang Bing will be rewarded first.